import {
  ForYouNav01,
  ForYouNav02,
  ForYouNav03,
  ForYouNav04,
  ForYouNav05,
  HowItWorks01,
  HowItWorks02,
  HowItWorks03,
  HowItWorks04,
  HomeHowItWorks01,
  HomeHowItWorks02,
  HomeHowItWorks03,
  HomeHowItWorks04,
  HowItWorksMobile01,
  HowItWorksMobile02,
  HowItWorksMobile03,
  MedicalTreatment01,
  MedicalTreatment02,
  MedicalTreatment03,
  MedicalTreatment04,
  MedicalTreatment05,
  MedicalTreatment06,
  MedicalTreatment07,
  NursingAndHomecareHowItWorks01,
  NursingAndHomecareHowItWorks02,
  OnlinePharmacyHowItWorks01,
  OnlinePharmacyHowItWorks02,
  OnlinePharmacyHowItWorks03,
  OnlinePharmacyHowItWorks04,
  NursingAndHomecareHowItWorks03,
  NursingAndHomecareHowItWorks04,
  DiagnosticsHowItWorks01,
  DiagnosticsHowItWorks02,
  DiagnosticsHowItWorks04,
  DiagnosticsHowItWorks03,
}
  from '../assets'


export const mentalHealthFAQData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "what-is-mental-illness",
    answer: "mental-illness-also-referred-to-as-mental-health-disorders-encompasses-various-mental-health-conditions-that-impact-our-self-perception-relationships-and-daily-functioning"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "what-are-most-common-symptoms-of-mental-illness",
    answer: "the-following-are-some-of-the-most-common-symptoms-of-mental-illness-changes-in-sleeping-or-eating-habits-withdrawal-from-family-and-friends-suicidal-thoughts-extreme-mood-swings-delusions-hallucinations-or-paranoia-excessive-alcohol-or-drug-use-difficulty-concentrating-confusion-or-feeling-lost-inability-to-cope-with-daily-stresses-feeling-sad-or-lethargic-loss-of-interest-in-activities-frequent-angry-outbursts-or-tantrums-hyperactivity-or-lack-of-energy-changes-in-work-or-school-performance"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "when-consult-for-mental-health",
    answer: "if-you-notice-signs-of-mental-illness-consult-with-our-doctors-to-receive-a-proper-diagnosis-and-treatment-early-intervention-can-prevent-symptoms-from-becoming-severe-mental-illnesses-with-mdhub-a-doctor-can-diagnose-your-condition-and-recommend-resources-like-psychotherapies-to-address-your-symptoms-if-necessary-they-can-also-prescribe-medication-to-manage-your-symptoms"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "what-other-services-mdhub-provides-for-mental-health",
    answer: "our-members-have-access-to-on-demand-mental-health-specialists-and-therapists-at-discounted-rates-in-addition-mdhub-members-can-use-headspace-app-with-no-additional-charge"
  },
]

export const virtualDoctorFAQData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'do-i-have-to-pay-to-consult-with-a-doctor',
    answer: 'our-members-have-24-7-access-to-online-doctors-at-no-additional-charge-they-also-benefit-from-discounted-rates-for-specialized-care'
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'is-it-possible-to-obtain-a-prescription-from-a-doctor-through-an-online-consultation',
    answer: 'if-youre-not-feeling-well-or-unable-to-reach-your-regular-doctor-for-a-prescription-refill-an-online-doctor-may-be-able-to-help-mdhub-ca-allows-you-to-have-a-remote-consultation-with-a-physician-who-can-prescribe-most-medications-online-except-for-controlled-substances-like-narcotics',
    secondParagraph: 'doctors-have-the-discretion-to-issue-prescriptions-online-once-you-receive-a-prescription-you-can-choose-to-have-it-delivered-to-your-door-for-free-or-pick-it-up-at-a-pharmacy-of-your-choice'
  },  
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'what-is-mdhub-virtual-doctor',
    answer: 'fast-and-convenient-access-to-canadian-licensed-doctors-nurse-practitioners-and-specialists-24-7-you-can-request-a-consultation-and-receive-a-diagnosis-treatment-plans-prescriptions-sick-notes-lab-requisitions-and-more-through-secure-text-messaging-audio-or-video-with-mdhub-get-a-prescription-in-minutes-at-the-providers-discretion-without-needing-a-referral-or-waitlist-to-see-a-specialist-online'
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'can-i-get-a-doctors-note',
    answer: "a-doctors-note-is-a-written-document-that-confirms-a-medical-condition-and-recommends-taking-time-off-to-recover-its-often-required-for-work-or-school-absences-as-proof-of-the-need-for-the-time-off-with-mdhub-you-can-obtain-a-doctors-note-or-sick-note-online-at-the-doctors-discretion-in-just-a-few-minutes"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'can-mdhub-doctors-give-blood-work-requisitions',
    answer: "our-virtual-doctors-can-issue-blood-test-requisitions-based-on-their-medical-judgment-and-what-they-consider-necessary-if-further-testing-is-needed-your-doctor-will-provide-a-requisition-form-during-your-online-consultation",
    secondParagraph: "after-the-test-the-results-will-be-sent-to-your-account-you-can-then-download-them-and-share-them-with-your-regular-doctor-or-request-another-virtual-visit-to-have-one-of-our-doctors-review-the-results-with-you"
  },
]

export const onlinePharmacyFAQData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "what-is-mdhubs-affiliate-online-pharmacy-and-why-should-i-use-it",
    answer: "mdhubs-affiliate-pharmacy-is-provided-through-industry-leading-pharmacy-partners-it-is-easy-and-convenient-you-can-get-started-with-our-online-process-and-youll-also-receive-a-personalized-welcome-call-to-ensure-that-your-experience-is-tailored-to-your-needs-keep-in-mind-that-if-you-have-a-physical-pharmacy-you-prefer-you-always-have-the-option-of-sending-your-prescriptions-there"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "can-i-talk-to-a-real-pharmacist",
    answer: "yes-you-have-access-to-a-team-of-licensed-pharmacists-accessible-by-phone-text-chat-and-email-and-you-can-use-our-24-7-emergency-phone-service"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "do-i-have-to-pay-to-use-the-online-pharmacy",
    answer: "no-there-is-no-additional-cost-to-use-our-online-pharmacy"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "how-do-i-get-a-prescription-or-renewal",
    answer: "mdhub-members-can-consult-with-our-online-doctors-anytime-from-anywhere-to-receive-a-prescription-or-renewal"
  }
]

export const diagnosticsFAQData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "do-i-need-a-requisition-for-blood-work-and-how-do-i-get-one",
    answer: "in-canada-a-licensed-doctor-is-required-to-give-you-a-requisition-to-get-bloodwork-done-our-online-doctors-can-provide-requisitions-online-and-will-decide-if-its-necessary-for-you"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "do-i-have-to-pay-for-the-lab-work",
    answer: "our-members-have-the-option-to-choose-between-public-and-private-laboratories-for-their-testing-requirements-additionally-we-offer-the-added-convenience-of-mobile-nursing-services-which-include-blood-sample-collection-from-the-comfort-of-your-own-home"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "can-mdhub-virtual-doctor-assist-interpreting-results",
    answer: "when-you-get-your-results-you-can-book-an-appointment-to-review-them-with-a-doctor-our-virtual-doctors-will-help-explain-the-results-and-your-next-steps"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "am-i-covered-by-my-private-insurance",
    answer: "most-private-insurance-companies-will-cover-the-expenses-associated-with-medical-laboratory-analyses-based-on-your-plan"
  }
]

export const nursingHomecareFAQData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "what-can-our-nurses-and-home-care-givers-do",
    answer: "mobile-nurses-and-home-caregivers-can-provide-a-variety-of-healthcare-services-and-support-to-patients-in-their-preferred-location-these-services-may-include-assistance-with-daily-living-activities-such-as-bathing-dressing-and-grooming-medication-administration-wound-care-vital-signs-monitoring-blood-sample-collection-injections-physical-therapy-exercises-and-other-medical-treatments-additionally-they-can-provide-emotional-support-companionship-and-communication-with-the-patients-healthcare-team-to-ensure-coordinated-care"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "am-i-covered-by-my-private-insurance",
    answer: "most-private-insurance-companies-will-cover-the-expenses-associated-with-medical-laboratory-analyses-based-on-your-plan"
}, 
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "how-does-home-care-service-work",
    answer: "each-time-a-personal-care-support-worker-from-mdhub-makes-a-service-visit-the-minimum-booking-duration-is-3-hours-this-is-the-minimum-number-of-hours-that-mdhub-provides-services-for-mdhub-believes-in-providing-a-top-quality-in-home-care-experience-which-is-achieved-through-consistency-in-the-people-who-visit-mdhub-strives-to-keep-the-same-caregivers-on-regular-and-consistent-schedules-as-much-as-possible-however-there-may-be-times-and-circumstances-beyond-our-control-that-require-us-to-assign-a-different-support-worker"
  }
]


export const nursingServices = [
  "vital signs monitoring",
  "Post Operative Care",
  "Oncology Care",
  "Urology Care",
  "IV Therapy",
  "Foot Care",
  "Injections & Infusions",
  "Vaccination",
  "In Home/Outdoors Assistance",
  "Blood Work & Testing",
  "Medication Administration/ Monitoring",
  "Companion Care",
  "Elderly Care",
  "Transportation Assistance"
]

export const homecareServices = [
  "In Home/Outdoors Assistance",
  "Medication Administration/ Monitoring",
  "Companion care",
  "Elderly care",
  "Transportation Assistance",
  "Light meal prepping/housekeeping"
]

export const forYouNavDetails = [
  {
    id: 1,
    image: ForYouNav01,
    title: "Medical Laboratory"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    image: ForYouNav02,
    title: "Virus Testing"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    image: ForYouNav03,
    title: "Online Pharmacist & Delivery"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    image: ForYouNav04,
    title: "Virtual Doctor"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    image: ForYouNav05,
    title: "Nursing & Homecare"
  },
]

export const howItWorksData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "Step 1",
    heading: "Sign up for a membership",
    image: HomeHowItWorks01,
    description: "Click on the “Sign Up” button and choose the membership type that works best for you. Then, answer a few questions about yourself.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "Step 2",
    heading: "Explore our dashboard",
    image: HomeHowItWorks02,
    description: "Go to your MDHUB dashboard. Here, you can access all your membership services: 24/7 virtual doctors, online pharmacy, lab testing, Headspace, and mental health help.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: "Step 3",
    heading: "Book an appointment",
    image: HomeHowItWorks03,
    description: "Get treated on the spot. Book an appointment with one of our specialists or see our mobile nurse offerings to have them come directly to you.",
  }
]

export const membershipBenefits = [
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "Unlimited access to doctors 24/7"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "Mental Healthcare"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: "Online Pharmacy"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    title: "Nursing and home care services"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    title: "Lab work and diagnostics"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    title: "Access to specialists"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    title: "Headspace app"
  },
]

export const medicalTreatmentData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "Diagnosis",
    image: MedicalTreatment01,
    text: "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur. Vulputate elementum eleifend sed morbi montes tristique."
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "Prescriptions & renewals",
    image: MedicalTreatment02,
    text: "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur. Vulputate elementum eleifend sed morbi montes tristique."
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: "Doctors notes",
    image: MedicalTreatment03,
    text: "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur. Vulputate elementum eleifend sed morbi montes tristique."
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    title: "Lab Requisitions",
    image: MedicalTreatment04,
    text: "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur. Vulputate elementum eleifend sed morbi montes tristique."
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    title: "Referrals to specialists",
    image: MedicalTreatment05,
    text: "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur. Vulputate elementum eleifend sed morbi montes tristique."
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    title: "Mental health",
    image: MedicalTreatment06,
    text: "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur. Vulputate elementum eleifend sed morbi montes tristique."
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    title: "General health advice",
    image: MedicalTreatment07,
    text: "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur. Vulputate elementum eleifend sed morbi montes tristique."
  },
]

export const virtualDoctorHowItWorksData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "Describe your symptoms using our app",
    description: "Open the app and click the “Get care” button. Describe your symptoms, and one of our healthcare providers will review your request in minutes.",
    image: HowItWorksMobile01
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "Chat with a doctor or nurse practitioner",
    description: "Typically, you’ll be connected with a healthcare provider over text, but they may request a video or audio chat if necessary.",
    image: HowItWorksMobile02
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: "Get a diagnosis or prescription",
    description: "Our virtual doctors can diagnose and provide prescriptions, and prescription delivery is available at no extra cost.",
    image: HowItWorksMobile03
  },
]

export const onlinePharmacyHowItWorksData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    text: "Once logged into your member dashboard, click online pharmacist.  Sign up and complete your health profile in 5 minutes.",
    image: OnlinePharmacyHowItWorks01
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    text: "We'll transfer your prescriptions from your old pharmacy, if required or will input new prescriptions obtained during virtual care consultation.",
    image: OnlinePharmacyHowItWorks02
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    text: "After verifying the prescription, we'll deliver your medicine directly to your door.",
    image: OnlinePharmacyHowItWorks03
  },
]

export const diagnosisHowItWorksData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    text: "patients-require-a-lab-requisition-if-you-dont-have-one-no-problem",
    image: DiagnosticsHowItWorks01
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    text: "Schedule a time and place for your testing and complete your payment online. Or you can visit a testing centre at no extra cost",
    image: DiagnosticsHowItWorks03
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    text: "Upload your requisition, and our medical staff will call you within 24 hours to confirm your booking.",
    image: DiagnosticsHowItWorks02
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    text: "Once testing is complete, our labs will submit your results to your virtual doctor with MDHUB.",
    image: DiagnosticsHowItWorks04
  },
]

export const nursingAndHomecareHowItWorksData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    text: "Describe or select your service.",
    image: NursingAndHomecareHowItWorks01
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    text: "Select a time and location",
    note: "Please note: Member pricing for nursing is $99 per visit, and $59 for homecare per hour",
    image: NursingAndHomecareHowItWorks02
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    text: "Complete payment",
    image: NursingAndHomecareHowItWorks03
  },
]
